{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The Press-Pull tool will ________ the face of a solid model in the direction it faces.", "opta": "taper", "optb": "extrude", "optc": "spiral", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The View toolbar will position the view of the 3-D solid toward the ________.", "opta": "front", "optb": "left side", "optc": "SE isometric", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Free Orbit tool is found on the ____ toolbar.", "opta": "rotate", "optb": "move", "optc": "modify", "optd": "3-D Move", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The default position of the UCS icon is positioned at ________ on the AutoCAD grid.", "opta": "0,0,0", "optb": "10,10,10", "optc": "20,20,20", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A cylinder can be created by drawing a rectangular shape then the ________ tool.", "opta": "Revolve", "optb": "Sweep", "optc": "Extrude", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The MASSPROP shortcut will provide the following information.", "opta": "mass", "optb": "volume", "optc": "bounding box", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The 3-D commands on the Modeling toolbar include ________.", "opta": "box", "optb": "sphere", "optc": "extrude", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CAD programs which incorporate parametric modeling utilize a system in which the dimensions control the ________.", "opta": "size and shape of the model features", "optb": "perspective of the model", "optc": "shading used to render the model", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order to create one solid model from two or more separate solid shapes the drafter will need to position them and then ________.", "opta": "use Union to join them", "optb": "use the Join command", "optc": "use the Add Parts tool", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Conceptual Visual Style tool is located on the ________ toolbar.", "opta": "Visual Styles", "optb": "Modify", "optc": "3-D Modeling", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}